Watch who you leave behind.
Abandon is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Stephen Gaghan.
A psychological thriller about a senior at one of
America's most prestigious universities.
Under enormous pressure to complete her thesis and earn a top job at one of the world's most competitive consulting
firms, Katie is still coping with the sudden unexplained disappearance of her first love two years prior.
As the investigation continues, Katie is forced to choose between past
passions and new possibilities, even as new facts are uncovered.
Katie Burke, played by Katie Holmes.
Wade Handler, played by Benjamin Bratt.
Embry Larkin, played by Charlie Hunnam.
Samantha Harper, played by Zooey Deschanel.
Bill Stayton, played by Fred Ward.
Robert Hanson, played by Mark Feuerstein.
Abandon is a 2002 American psychological thriller drama film written
and directed by Stephen Gaghan in his directorial debut.
It follows a college student (Katie Holmes) whose boyfriend
(Charlie Hunnam) disappeared two years previously.
Despite being set at an American university, much of the movie was filmed
in Montreal, Quebec at McGill University's McConnell Hall.
It is based on the book Adams Fall by Sean Desmond.
The book was re-titled Abandon for the movie tie-in paperback printing.
The film co-stars Zooey Deschanel, Gabrielle Union, and Melanie Lynskey, with Benjamin Bratt
playing the detective who is investigating the boyfriend's disappearance.
It was a critical and commercial failure.
The film explores themes of dancer, nightmare, alcohol, detective, college.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.